{
    "subject": "resource/Doctor_Who",
    "predicate": "property/network",
    "object": "resource/BBC_One",
    "human_readable": "The network of Doctor Who is BBC One.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7334524393081665,
            "question": "Is Doctor Who a BBC production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7255731821060181,
            "question": "Which network is associated with the show Doctor Who?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6370635628700256,
            "question": "What channel has aired Doctor Who?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6091995239257812,
            "question": "What is the network responsible for broadcasting Doctor Who?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5551727414131165,
            "question": "What television network broadcasts Doctor Who?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4142993092536926,
            "question": "What is the primary broadcaster of Doctor Who?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3825555741786957,
            "question": "On which channel does Doctor Who air?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27783477306365967,
            "question": "Who produces Doctor Who?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21316473186016083,
            "question": "Where can you watch episodes of Doctor Who?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09596226364374161,
            "question": "Is BBC One known for science fiction programming?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The network of Doctor Who is BBC One.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4653_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you watch episodes of Doctor Who?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4653_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who produces Doctor Who?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4653_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=On which channel does Doctor Who air?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4653_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4653_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4653_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4653_136.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4653_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4653_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4653_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4653_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4653_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4653_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4653_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support this triple. According to the text, Doctor Who is a British television series that airs on BBC One in the UK, among other platforms."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the series Doctor Who airs on BBC One in the UK and will also be available on Disney+. This supports the statement that the network of Doctor Who is BBC One."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}